speed-find.com 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy, Cookies and Data Protection

Privacy Policy, Cookies and Data Protection

Last updated on: Agust 31, 2015

AD BUSINESS CROWN SOLUTIONS, SL strictly observes current legislation in matters of data protection, and particularly the Directive 95/46/EC for Personal Data Protection, adopting on that regard, the technical and organizational measures deemed necessary to avoid the loss, misuse, alteration and, non-authorized access to the provided personal data, in this case, through the Web, guaranteeing the confidentiality of its details.

We respect your privacy, and we understand the importance of the information you entrust to us. This Privacy Policy describes our practices concerning the information collected by the extension. Below we describe what information we collect when you use our Services, how we protect that information, how long we retain it, with whom we share it, and what your privacy options are. By using the Services, you consent to our collection and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We will continue to evaluate this Privacy Policy against new technologies, business practices, and our users’ needs, and may make changes to the Privacy Policy accordingly. Please check this page periodically for updates. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy here, along with its effective date. Your continued use of the Services after our posting of changes to this Privacy Policy means that you agree to be bound by such changes.

  1\. What information do we collect about you?

The advertising component developed by AD BUSINESS CROWN SOLUTIONS, SL (see End User Licence Agreement “Terms of Use”) monitors and keeps the navigation and search habits of the computer's user where it is installed. During this data collection, it is possible that personal data may be gathered depending on the browsing habits that the user may have and the web pages that s/he may visit not being the final purpose of the software.

With this information, AD BUSINESS CROWN SOLUTIONS, SL will not be able to identify the user.The data which you provide may be incorporated into a file under the responsibility of AD BUSINESS CROWN SOLUTIONS, SL with the aim of offering and managing the software's service and/or product.

Supplying any personal data through the different forms of this software implies expressly accepting and consenting to the processing of the aforementioned data' under the given terms and with the described aims. Any delivery of commercial electronic communications takes place in strict accordance with current legislation in matters regarding communications and e-commerce.

The collected data is appropriate, pertinent and non-excessive regarding the scope, the aims and theparticular, explicit and lawful services provided by AD BUSINESS CROWN SOLUTIONS, SL, it is stated in the forms, at all times, the compulsory and the optional details and -if necessary- the particular conditions for the service which may be additional to those present when the user is registering.

AD BUSINESS CROWN SOLUTIONS, SL commits itself to a duty of secrecy and confidentiality regarding the personal data contents of the automatic file in accordance with the applicable legislation, likewise, it commits itself to confer a secure treatment to those transfers which may, in some cases, happen.

Also, if you choose to login to a product or feature accessed through a Search Application via a social networking site, you are granting us permission to access and use information about you provided by the social network. For example, if you use a social network feature to login to a product accessed through a Search Application, per such social network’s policies, they may provide us access to you and your friends names, pictures, genders, user Ids, connections and any content shared using an “Everyone” or similar privacy setting. Please be aware, that by posting information to message boards, chat groups or social networking facilities available via the Services, you will be making this information available to other users of these Services to the public. You should be careful about revealing any sensitive details about yourself.

Information We Collect When You Use The Services:  
When you use the Services, we automatically collect and store certain information about your computer or device and your activities, This information can include:

  1. IP address of your computer
  2. Unique mobile device identifier
  3. Technical information about your computer or mobile device such as type of device, mobile device ID number, web browser (Internet Explorer 8, etc.), other browser information (e.g. size, connection speed and connection type), and operating system or platform (Mac, Windows XP, etc.)
  4. Your preferences and settings (time zone, language, etc.)
  5. Internet provider or mobile carrier name
  6. The URL of the webpages visited and titles
  7. Information about your activity on the Services (e.g., your search queries, mis-formatted DNS entries, search results selected, clicks, pages viewed, search history, comments);
  8. We may also collect information about that Search Application (e.g. the specific release date and distribution source of your Search Application, a unique Search Application ID, Search Application partner ID, the ads you click on, and information contained in error log files or cookies, aggregate query or click data and erroneous domain name system requests).

  2\. How do we use the information we collect?

We use the information we collect from and about you for a variety of purposes, including to:

  * verify your eligibility for our Services;
  * respond to your queries with the best possible answers and search results;
  * understand our users (their demographics, what they do on our Services, what features they like, how they use them etc.) and improve our Services, such as by personalizing content to your interests and process and complete your transactions;
  * administer our Services, diagnose technical problems and otherwise manage our business;
  * distinguish your Search Application for purposes of compensating third parties who distributedthe Search Application on our behalf and to analyze retention and usage per distribution partner or channel;
  * send you communications that you have requested or that may be of interest to you in accordance with your preferences. Please see the section “Reviewing, changing or deleting information” for further information about how you can control these communications;
  * send you questions from other users that you may be able to answer if you have registered with our Services;
  * identify an interest or intention on a brand/product/service/content
  * provide you with customer support;
  * enable us to show you ads that are more relevant to you; and
  * perform functions as otherwise described at the time of collection.

We may also generate, use and disclose aggregated and/or anonymized information and statistics about your use of the Services to third parties for marketing, analytical and strategic purposes.

  3\. How do we share the information we collect?

We will share your information in the following ways:

  * **Our Search Application partners:** If you have installed a Search Application, our Application partners may collect / receive information about you including the queries you submit via the Services, the Search Application functionality and / or website, the version of your Search Application or your browser settings, the search results and ads you click on, and the address of the web pages you previously visited.
  * **Fraud prevention:** We may disclose the personal information we collect about our userswe believe disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or respond to suspected illegal or fraudulent activity or to protect the safety, rights, or property of us, our users, or others.
  * **Law enforcement purposes:** If requested or required by government authorities, such as enforcement authorities, courts, or regulators, or otherwise to comply with the law, we may disclose any information we have about our users. We also may disclose information collected about you in order to exercise or protect legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * **Advertisers and advertising networks:** establish commercial communication by its own or third parties (Desktop, Mobile, etc) and formats (RTB, Search, Display, Video, Email, Content Advertising, etc). With the same end, it will try to provide those commercial communications from third parties which may have the user's personal data and previous authorization. With this aim, an algorithm will be used to encrypt, in an unintelligible way, any information collected which, compared with the information from these third parties, may allow to elaborate more effective adverts addressed in accordance with the preferences of the computer user.

  4\. Cookies and Online Advertising:

We use cookies, pixel tags, web beacons and other such similar technologies to collect and store the information we automatically collect about your computer, device and Service usage. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer and a pixel tag (also called a web beacon or clear GIF) is a tiny graphic with a unique identifier, embedded invisibly on a webpage (or an online ad or email). We use the term “cookies” in this policy to refer to cookies and all such similar technologies.

A cookie is a file which is downloaded and stored in the computer to allow us, among other things, to store and recover information about the user's browsing habits or that of his/her equipment's and, depending on the information contained and the way in which the equipment is used. Our website can only establish cookies in his/her computer if his/her search engine allows so.

There are two broad categories of cookies: (1) first party cookies, served directly by us to your computer or mobile device, and (2) third party cookies, which are served by a third party on our behalf. Cookies have a lot of jobs. For example, our cookies enable us to recognize you (e.g. as a registered user) when you visit our website and to store your preferences and settings. We use third party cookies for functionality, performance / analytics, advertising and social media purposes. Cookies from advertising companies, for example, help to ensure that the advertisements you see online are more relevant to you and your interests.

In accordance with current legislation, we inform you that our software and our website include an advertising system or component consisting of an advertising cookie which allows us to identify the web page which the user is visiting with the aim of showing him/her advertising or informative messages through our software which may interest him/her while s/he searches, receiving the best offers of the day on the internet in his internet browsing window. Our website can only establish cookies in his/her computer if his/her search engine allows so.

In addition to technical and personalisation cookies which are essential for the correct working of our website, we use cookies with the following aims:

  * Analysis Cookies: they are only used to quantify the number of users accessing this website, simplifying the measuring and statistical analysis which may allow us to improve the offer of products and services in the Web-Site.
  * Advertising Cookies: They allow us to manage the offer of our own advertising spaces and that of our collaborators, matching the content of the advert to the content of the service requested or to the use made of our web page. This is done in accordance with his/her Internet browsing habits, being able, therefore, to show him/her adverts related to his search profile.
  * Behavioural advertising cookies: We allow run as efficiently as possible and advertising space to third-party websites accessed by the user. These cookies store information on user behaviour obtained by monitoring your browsing habits, allowing to develop a specific profile to display ads based on the same.

The analysis cookies for third parties that we use in our website are:

  * Google Analytics cookie analysis that enables monitoring and analysis of user behavior.
  * Ad Businness Crown Solutions SL: analytical cookies advertising and behavioral advertising according to its navigation features.
  * Cookie AppNexus: advertising cookie that provides advertisements in your browser.
  * Cookie DoubleClick: ad cookie that provides advertisements in your browser.
  * Cookies DoubleClick for Advertisers (DFA): cookie to track advertising displayed in your browser.

The installation of cookies is always done if and only if the user authorises in his/her search engine the installation, not only in his pages but also on those connected with or referenced recently through the use of links, without collecting at any given time personal or confidential user data or behavioural profiles, guaranteeing the anonymity of the user.

How To Control Or Delete Cookies:

Most browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. Users can usually set their browsers to block all third-party cookies (which are those set by third-party companies collecting information on websites operated by other companies), block all cookies (including first-party cookies), or block specific cookies. These settings will typically be found in the “options” or “preferences” menu of your browser. In order to understand these settings, the following links may be helpful, otherwise you should use the “Help” option in your browser for more details.

  * [Cookie settings in Safari web](http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042) and [iOS.](http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677)

Please note that if you choose to block cookies, this may interfere with certain functionality on our website. Also, if you have disabled one or more cookies, we may still use information collected from cookies prior to your disabled preference being set; however, we will stop using the disabled cookie to collect any further information.

Third parties whose products or services are accessible or advertised through the Services, including social networking services, may also use cookies or similar tools, and we advise you to check their privacy policies for information about their cookies and other practices. We do not control the practices of such partners and their privacy policies govern their interactions with you. We encourage you to read their privacy policies.

**Online Behavioral Advertising and Mobile.** Advertisers and advertising networks place ads (including sponsored links in search results) on our website. These companies, as well as data analytics companies who service them, may use cookies, pixel tags, mobile device IDs and other similar technologies to collect data about you when you visit our site. They use the data to enable them to track your activity across various sites where they display ads and record your activities, so they can show ads that they consider relevant to you. You may opt-out of receiving targeted online advertising from advertising networks by visiting the following websites:

  * Network Advertising Initiative [(http://www.networkadvertising.org/)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)
  * Digital Advertising Alliance [(http://www.aboutads.info/consumers)](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers)

Please bear in mind that there are many more companies listed on these sites than those that drop cookies on our website.

  5\. Reviewing, changing or deleting information

The User may use his/her rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition to the treatment of his/her personal data by sending a petition to adbusinesscrownsolutions@gmail.com or by letter to AD BUSINESS CROWN SOLUTIONS, SL located at Calle General Ramirez de Madrid 8, 28020, Madrid, Spain.

**Do Not Track.** Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. DNT is a way for users to inform websites and services that they do not want certain information about their webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. We are committed to providing you with meaningful choices about the information collected on our website for third party purposes, and that is why we provide the Network Advertising Initiative and the Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out links above. However, we do not recognize or respond to browser-initiated DNT signals, as the Internet industry is currently still working toward defining exactly what DNT means, what it means to comply with DNT, and a common approach to responding to DNT.

  6\. How do we keep the information we collect secure?

We take the security of your personal information seriously and use appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information against unauthorized or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage. We also limit access to personal information about you to employees who reasonably need access to it to provide products or services to you, or in order to do their jobs. However, because no security system can be 100% effective, we cannot completely guarantee the security of any information we may have collected from or about you.

  7\. How long do we keep the information we collect?

We retain the information we collect about and from you for as long as necessary to fulfill a business purpose or comply with a legal request. We may also choose to anonymize certain of the information you provide to us so that it can no longer be attributed to you if we would like to retain it for longer periods of time.
